<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Boston: A Guide for Touring Musicians</string>
    <string name="category_blogs">Music Blogs</string>
    <string name="category_eat">Eat</string>
    <string name="category_venues">Venues</string>
    <string name="category_fests">Fests</string>
    <string name="category_bars">Bars</string>
    <string name="boston">Tour Van Boston</string>
    <string name="about_boston">About Boston, MA</string>
    <!-- Info from wikipedia.com -->
    <string name="city">Boston is the capital city and most populous municipality[9] of the
        Commonwealth of Massachusetts in the United States. The city proper covers 48 square miles
        (124 km2) with an estimated population of 685,094 in 2017,[3] making it also the most
        populous city in the New England region.[2] Boston is the seat of Suffolk County as well,
        although the county government was disbanded on July 1, 1999.[10] The city is the economic
        and cultural anchor of a substantially larger metropolitan area known as Greater Boston, a
        metropolitan statistical area (MSA) home to a census-estimated 4.8 million people in 2016
        and ranking as the tenth-largest such area in the country.[11] As a combined statistical
        area (CSA), this wider commuting region is home to some 8.2 million people, making it the
        sixth-largest in the United States.[12]</string>
    <string name="skyline">Zagat Bridge</string>
    <string name="sky">sky</string>
    <string name="weather_in_boston">Weather in Boston</string>
    <string name="seasons">Boston is the epitome of a Northeastern city: the weather changes
        radically from season to season, the city is populated with diverse groups of people and
        nearly every street is home to a historical site. Finding things to do in Boston is easy,
        but packing is harder. Bring clothing loose enough to walk in, warm enough to stay
        comfortable and stylish enough to fit into Boston's chic nightlife scene.</string>
    <string name="image_of_item">Image of Item</string>
    <string name="dividing_bar">Dividing Bar</string>
    <string name="vanyaland">VANYALAND</string>
    <string name="vanyaland_address">Boston, MA</string>
    <string name="vanyaland_phone">(617) 867–5309</string>
    <string name="vanyaland_info">Vanyaland is for connected individuals who are “culture-forward”
        and looking to discover a definitive news, lifestyle, and entertainment source in their
        city and beyond.</string>
    <string name="vanyaland_website">www.vanyaland.com</string>
    <string name="hassle">BOSTON HASSLE</string>
    <string name="hassle_address">Boston, MA</string>
    <string name="pudding">ALLSTON PUDDING</string>
    <string name="pudding_address">Allston, MA</string>
    <string name="hassle_phone">(617) 867–5309</string>
    <string name="pudding_phone">(617) 867–5309</string>
    <string name="hassle_website">www.bostonhassle.com</string>
    <string name="pudding_website">www.allstonpudding.com</string>
    <string name="hassle_info">Boston Hassle is part of Brain Arts Organization which is an arts and
        music organization brought to you by musicians, artists, writers, and enthusiasts in the
        Greater Boston Area. We compile and maintain a daily, curated list of music, art and film
        happenings and works in Boston, New England, and beyond.</string>
    <string name="pudding_info">
        Welcome to Allston Pudding, your online source for music both in Boston and beyond! Allston
        Pudding is operated and written by fans and musicians to highlight new music and live music
        from all over. We are supporters of local music, from our hometown to local scenes
        throughout the world. We hope to support and champion artists who may not receive their
        proper radio play or publicity, but definitely deserve your attention.
        Take a read and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="taco">TACO PARTY</string>
    <string name="lifealive">LIFE ALIVE</string>
    <string name="wholeheart">WHOLE HEART PROVISIONS</string>
    <string name="taco_address">711 Broadway\nSomerville, MA</string>
    <string name="lifealive_address">765 Massachusetts Ave\nCambridge, MA</string>
    <string name="wholeheart_address">487 Cambridge Street\nAllston, MA</string>
    <string name="taco_phone">(617) 764–0683</string>
    <string name="lifealive_phone">(617) 354–5433</string>
    <string name="wholeheart_phone">(617) 202–5041</string>
    <string name="taco_website">www.tacopartytruck.com</string>
    <string name="lifealive_website">www.lifealive.com</string>
    <string name="wholeheart_website">www.wholeheartprovisions.com/</string>
    <string name="taco_info">Colorful, kitschy counter-serve spot with a meatless Mexican menu
        starring inventive veggie tacos.</string>
    <string name="lifealive_info">Friendly, funky, quick-serve spot for organic veggie/vegan wraps,
        salads and smoothies.</string>
    <string name="wholeheart_info">Build-your-own bowls of veggies, grains and unique toppings at this
        fast-casual, vegan-friendly spot.</string>
    <string name="hasslefest">HASSLE FEST</string>
    <string name="bostoncalling">BOSTON CALLING</string>
    <string name="roxbury">ROXBURY ROCKS</string>
    <string name="hasslefest_address">156 Highland Ave\nSomerville, MA</string>
    <string name="bostoncalling_address">65 North Harvard St\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="roxbury_address">1234 Columbus Ave\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="hasslefest_phone">(617) 867–5309</string>
    <string name="bostoncalling_phone">(888) 512–7469</string>
    <string name="roxbury_phone">(617) 427–0060</string>
    <string name="hasslefest_website">www.http://bostonhasslefest.com/</string>
    <string name="bostoncalling_website">www.bostoncalling.com</string>
    <string name="roxbury_website">www.roxburyrocks.weebly.com</string>
    <string name="hasslefest_info">Brain Arts and Boston Hassle’s annual celebration of the music and art
        underground of America (and beyond). Anti-commercial, independent, and outsider culture is
        our culture. 2 day good time in Boston, MA. A chance to get the freaks together.</string>
    <string name="bostoncalling_info">Boston Calling Music Festival is a Boston-based music festival.
        Debuting in May 2013, Boston Calling previously took place twice a year, May and September,
        at City Hall Plaza. It attracted 20-22,000 fans with each edition.</string>
    <string name="roxbury_info">Roxbury Rocks! is a student-run service project founded in fall 2015
        by Tallie Hausser, an incoming Northeastern University freshman in the University Scholars
        Program.  Comprised this year of 7 University Scholars – four of which are first-years –,
        RR! is both a research project and a community service undertaking, whose aim is expose
        children of all backgrounds to music and dance education.</string>
    <string name="greatscott">GREAT SCOTT</string>
    <string name="sinclair">SINCLAIR</string>
    <string name="paradise">PARADISE ROCK CLUB</string>
    <string name="greatscott_address">1222 Commonwealth Avenue\nAllston, MA</string>
    <string name="sinclair_address">52 Church Street\nCambridge, MA</string>
    <string name="paradise_address">967 Commonwealth Ave\nBoston, MA</string>
    <string name="greatscott_phone">(617) 566 9014</string>
    <string name="sinclair_phone">(617) 547–5200</string>
    <string name="paradise_phone">(617) 562–8800</string>
    <string name="greatscott_website">www.greatscottboston.com/</string>
    <string name="sinclair_website">www.sinclaircambridge.com</string>
    <string name="paradise_website">www.paradisrock.club</string>
    <string name="greatscott_info">Low-key destination for indie-underground live-music shows and long-running dance nights.</string>
    <string name="sinclair_info">This gastropub and music venue features New American fare and live acts, with an open kitchen and patio.</string>
    <string name="paradise_info">The Paradise Rock Club is a 933-capacity music venue located in Boston, Massachusetts. Because of its relatively small size,
        it appeals to top local rock and alternative performers as well as American bands visiting Boston for the first time.</string>
    <string name="model">MODEL CAFE</string>
    <string name="auto">THE AUTOMATIC</string>
    <string name="ellum">DEEP ELLUM</string>
    <string name="model_address">7 N Beacon Street\nBoston MA</string>
    <string name="auto_address">50 Hampshire Street\nCambridge, MA</string>
    <string name="ellum_address">477 Cambridge Street\nAllston, MA</string>
    <string name="model_phone">(617) 254–9365</string>
    <string name="auto_phone">(617) 714–5226</string>
    <string name="ellum_phone">(617) 787–233</string>
    <string name="model_website">www.palmettocarriage.com</string>
    <string name="auto_website">www.charlestonculinarytours.com</string>
    <string name="ellum_website">www.deepellum-allston.com/dewp/</string>
    <string name="model_info">Cocktails and beers come in a bare-bones setting with a variety of bar games including pinball.</string>
    <string name="auto_info">Charleston Culinary Tours combine the best of Charleston history,
        cocktails and food with unique tours that highlight the Lowcountry. On each tour, you
        will not only have an opportunity to sample some of the Lowcountry\'s finest offerings,
        but also to meet the owners, chefs and mixologists behind Charleston\'s impressive culinary
        and bar innovations.</string>
    <string name="ellum_info">Here at Ghost City, we are proud to offer our ghost tours in South
        Carolina\'s most haunted city! Our Charleston Ghost Tours take you to the most haunted
        locations in the downtown area of Charleston. You\'ll hear the stories of Charleston\'s
        haunted history while standing in the very places these haunting events take place.</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="weather">Weather</string>
</resources>
